Hello friends, I have a question
that is very common, it is covered in panels like CGHS and many other such
panels,
so the answer to this will be given to you in this video,
I, Dr Abhishek Goyal, welcome all of you to
this channel,
see everyone asks a question that sir, the
LASIK laser surgery that we get done, can it be
covered in any of our panels or health insurance, the
simple answer to this is no, it is not covered in any medical
insurance health package or any government
panel that you have,
now a question will come to your mind that
sir, why is this LASIK or laser surgery
not covered, see, this government
of ours, which is the
government of India, believes that LASIK or
laser surgery is a cosmetic surgery,
it is not a necessary surgery, these
people who do not want to wear glasses for any reason, that is, there are
many people who
say for not wearing glasses that sir, we get marks on our nose, we become heavy
or someone wants to
go to the Air Force or someone wants to
go to the Railways, so many such people  There are
many different reasons for not
wearing glasses, that is why people get surgery done,
so this surgery
comes under cosmetic surgery, that is why the
Government of India calls it
cosmetic surgery, that is why it is not covered in any health
package or medical insurance
or any panel, I
hope that whatever other question you have in your mind
related to this, you
can ask me by commenting and
I must have answered all the questions you had in your mind,
thank you.